[
    {
        "question": "Where is the world`s oldest continuous underground fire?",
        "answer": "Australia -- A 6,000-year-old fire beneath the surface is the world`s oldest known underground fire that is still burning."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many countries share common borders with India?",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "The names of how many countries start with the letter `A`?",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many countries does Afghanistan border?",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Saint Vincent and the Grenadines?",
        "answer": "Kingstown"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is known as `The Insurance Capital of the World`?",
        "answer": "Hartford, Connecticut"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Mauritania?",
        "answer": "Nouakchott"
    },
    {
        "question": "What three provinces requested a single Dominion be formed in 1867, thus beginning to shape modern Canada?",
        "answer": "New Brunswick, Nova Scotia and the Province of Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "What distiller and entrepreneur founded the town of Walkerville, which is now a heritage neighborhood of Windsor, Ontario in Canada?",
        "answer": "Hiram Walker"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which large Canadian city is named after a fruit-bearing shrub native to western Canada, Alaska and northern United States?",
        "answer": "Saskatoon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city became the first capital of the Province of Canada in 1841?",
        "answer": "Kingston, Ontario"
    },
    {
        "question": "What island is the most populous in Canada?",
        "answer": "Island of Montreal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which European countries have an enclave with each other in the region of Baarle-Nassau?",
        "answer": "Belgium and The Netherlands (Holland)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the oldest city in the world?",
        "answer": "Damascus (The capital of Syria has evidence of continuous habitation dating back at least 11,000 years)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What mountain is nicknamed the `Savage Mountain`?",
        "answer": "K-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest waterfall in Europe?",
        "answer": "Krimml Waterfalls"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city is Ebenezer Baptist Church, where Martin Luther King Jr. and his father were pastors?",
        "answer": "Atlanta"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where would you find the King`s Palace, the Papoose Room, and the Witch`s Finger?",
        "answer": "Carlsbad Caverns"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2004, a nine-foot-tall bronze statue of Bobby Bowden was dedicated in what US city?",
        "answer": "Tallahassee"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Greenland called by its Inuit native residents?",
        "answer": "Kaallalit Nunaat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Armenia is considered to be part of which continent?",
        "answer": "Asia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two countries would you find Andorra sandwiched between?",
        "answer": "Spain and France"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country would you find the informally named `The Enver Hoxha Mausoleum` landmark?",
        "answer": "Albania"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the southern equivalent of the Northern Lights?",
        "answer": "Aurora Australis or Southern Lights"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the highest airport in the U.S.?",
        "answer": "Colorado -- of the more than 5,000 public airports in the U.S., Leadville-Lake County Airport is the highest at 9,945 ft"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. state is home to the geometric bridge named High Trestle Trail Bridge?",
        "answer": "Iowa -- The bridge connects Woodward to Ankeny, Iowa and crosses the Des Moines River."
    },
    {
        "question": "In which U.S. state can you find a river nicknamed the `River of No Return`?",
        "answer": "Idaho"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which beach was featured in the movie `The Beach` starring Leonardo DiCaprio?",
        "answer": "Maya Bay in Thailand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you find the only piece of artwork Michaelangelo ever signed?",
        "answer": "St. Peter`s Basilica in Vatican City"
    },
    {
        "question": "What royal has the most places in Canada named for him or her?",
        "answer": "Queen Victoria -- She reigned from 1837 to 1901, but never visited Canada, although several of her children did."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has a museum dedicated to Arnold Schwarzenegger?",
        "answer": "Austria -- He grew up in the village of Thal, near Austria`s second largest city of Graz."
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country are `Democracy Sausages` sold at polls on election day?",
        "answer": "Australia -- As a result of compulsory voting, food vendors popped up at poling places. Sausages made their debut in the 1980s."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two European countries border the Bay of Biscay?",
        "answer": "Spain and France -- The coastline includes numerous sandy beaches with particularly good conditions for surfing."
    },
    {
        "question": "The 200-foot-tall Palouse Falls is located in which U.S. state?",
        "answer": "Washington -- Located in Palouse Falls State Park, the roughly 13,000-year-old waterfall is part of the Palouse River."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the official language of Papua New Guinea?",
        "answer": "English"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the English translation of the area of Cuba called Bahia de Cochinos?",
        "answer": "Bay of Pigs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state, one of the original 13 colonies, has a flag featuring an anchor surrounded by 13 stars?",
        "answer": "Rhode Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest island in the Mediterranean Sea?",
        "answer": "Sicily"
    },
    {
        "question": "What European city is known as the `Eternal City`?",
        "answer": "Rome"
    },
    {
        "question": "Concord is the capital of which US state?",
        "answer": "New Hampshire"
    },
    {
        "question": "Buzzards Bay separates mainland Massachusetts from what land mass?",
        "answer": "Cape Cod"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Ivy League school is located in Massachusetts?",
        "answer": "Harvard"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest inland lake in South America?",
        "answer": "Titicaca"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many rivers does Saudi Arabia have?",
        "answer": "None"
    },
    {
        "question": "What name is given to a triangular or fanlike river?",
        "answer": "Delta"
    },
    {
        "question": "The coat of arms on Michigan`s state flag is held by an elk and what other animal?",
        "answer": "Moose -- The flag also features an eagle. Moose are native to the state. Elk were introduced in 1911."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which state`s flag features an indigineous tribe`s symbol for the sun?",
        "answer": "New Mexico -- It features bright yellow background with the Zia Pueblo people`s symbol for the sun in the middle."
    },
    {
        "question": "What U.S. state has the only non-rectangular state flag?",
        "answer": "Ohio -- The Buckeye State`s state flag is triangular and tapers into a swallowtail shape at the end."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest mountain in Africa?",
        "answer": "Mount Kilimanjaro"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the state flower of Florida?",
        "answer": "Orange blossom -- Oranges are a billion-dollar business in Florida, and Florida has chosen to honor all parts of the orange tree."
    }
]